原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译    春天里的小熊  薇薇安  PiPi  徐棒棒  ABCpril
翻译    普利星布里狗  高庭玫瑰  肉塔  木浅  宜九零
精校       丶胜天半子丶的丶何何丶
校对       木浅     普利星布里狗     匡老师是厕所校对王
时间轴     姜姜  大葱  壬虚浪影  WEB版轴：何何丶
后期      渔夫   V2后期   何何丶乃丶展大侠  是也
总监      丶胜天半子丶的丶何何丶
最新海外影视剧下载
我们会把你救出来的
We're gonna get you out of here.
你为我们安排好出去的路了吗
是的  就在明晚
波塞冬把我们安排到这里去救拉马尔
Poseidon put us in here to get Ramal out,
但他又抛弃了我们
but then he abandoned us.
拉马尔是波塞冬的人  不是我们的
Ramal is Poseidon's guy, not ours.
越狱开始了
The escape is on.
他是我哥
He's my brother!
这个波塞冬到底是何方神圣
Who the hell is this Poseidon guy?
中情局里一名不得志的政策专家
A frustrated policy wonk
他在中情局内创建了一个
in the CIA, who created a cell
叫"21号空间"的组织
within the CIA called 21-Void.
而他需要我的帮助
And he needed my help
联调局&中情局通缉令
卡尼尔·乌提斯
在世界各地把入狱的人救出来
breaking out people imprisoned all over the world.
我们触发了一些事
We've awoken something.
波塞冬有没有可能让我们直接杀了她
Any chance Poseidon will just let us kill her?
-请指认  -3号和4号
- Point. - It's three and four.
那一男一女就是枪手
The man, and the woman was the shooter.
-退后  -想都别想
- Step back! - ‭That's not gonna happen.
去死吧
Go to hell!
我们赶紧离开这里
Let's get the hell out of here!
现在逃离的唯一办法就是坐飞机  兄弟
The only way out now is up, brother.
对不起  对不起  兄弟
I'm so sorry. Sorry, brother.
也门  萨那
我们得抓紧行动
We got to move.
不行  我们今晚要是走上街去就死定了
No. We go out on the streets tonight, we're dead.
你我心知肚明
You know it and I know it.
就算出了监狱
Even on the outside,
还是觉得整个世界都沦为狭小的空间
I feel the world crushing in.
在监狱里待久了就会这样
That's what being locked up does.
你永远感觉自己身在监狱里
You carry the prison with you on the outside.
我不能那样生活
I can't live that way.
我得知道监狱高墙已不复存在
I've got to know the walls disappear.
你那是害怕  你不嗑药清醒时就能感觉到
It's called being scared. Happens when you're sober.
少拿我嗑药说事
Don't give me the pill talk.
我不会拿你孤儿的身份说事
I won't give you the poor little orphan talk.
我也不会告诉你
How your friend here
你的朋友并不是你期待的父亲形象
isn't the father figure you thought he was gonna be.
吵是没有用的
This isn't helping.
高墙会离我们远去的  兄弟
The walls are going away, brother.
我们要让它们消失殆尽
We're gonna make 'em go away.
我们要离开这个国家
We're getting out of this country.
所有人
All of us.
是吗  你又想用哪个应急方案啊
Oh, really? Which contingency's that gonna be?
你已经都试过了
You burned through them all.
乘货车  火车  飞机离开边境
Truck to border, train, airport.
哪个都不用
None of those.
我们现在的处境是我最不想要的
We're exactly where I don't want to be:
即兴发挥
improvising.
那我们真得快点即兴发挥
Well, we need to improvise something real fast
不然在那边被吊死的
or it's gonna be us down there,
就会是我们
strung up like that.
奥玛  希巴的人
Omar. Sheba's guy.
她说他有办法出去
She said he had a way out.
我们能信任他吗
We can trust him?
不能  但他是我们最后的选择了
No. But he's our last option.
纽约  惠特尼海兹
惠特尼海兹警局
你被保释了  可以出狱了
You made bail. You're being released.
别当不认识啊  甜心
Don't be a stranger, sugar.
惠特尼海兹警局
波塞冬先把你弄出来了
Poseidon got you out first.
我原以为我才是他的最爱呢
I thought I was his favorite.
这狗日的真逃出来了
Son of a bitch really escaped.
是的
Yep.
但为什么杀了拉马尔  我还以为他们是一伙的
But why kill Ramal? I thought they were allies.
干我们这行的  不该问的别问
It's not our job to ask questions.
或许我们应该问
Maybe we should.
波塞冬命令我们找到卡尼尔·乌提斯  杀了他
Poseidon says we find Kaniel Outis and kill him.
这才是我们要做的事
That's what we're gonna do.
我想我知道该怎么做了
And I think I know how to do it.
奥玛
Omar.
你来这做什么
What are you doing here?
到处都在通缉你  朋友
You're radioactive, my friend.
你杀了阿布·拉马尔  是真的吗
You killed Abu Ramal. Really?
那可不是明智之举
That was a very stupid move, man.
你只要告诉我们要去哪
Just tell us where you're headed.
穿越沙漠483公里  到费阿刻斯
300 miles across the desert. Phaeacia.
干走私的老朋友
Old smuggling friends.
自治领地  没有ISIL的人
Uh, autonomous zone. No ISIL.
完美
Perfect.
不完美
Not perfect.
你们四个  我一个  位子不够
Four of you, one of me. Not enough seats.
好吧好吧  再弄一辆车怎么样
Okay, okay, all right. What about getting another vehicle?
我跟你们说啊
Tell you what.
因为希巴的关系  我欠她人情
Because it's Sheba and I owe her,
或许我们能互相帮助
maybe we can help each other.
我还有一辆车
I have another vehicle.
一辆丰田"陆巡"
A Land Cruiser.
我本来要丢下它的
I was going to leave it behind,
但如果你们能把它弄来
but if you can get it,
它在一个距这两个街区的停车场
it's in a parking garage two blocks from here.
我会让你们跟着的
I'll let you follow.
带来我的第二辆车
Deliver my second vehicle,
或许我会让费阿刻斯人给你们弄艘船
and maybe I get the Phaeacians to get you a boat somewhere,
到欧洲法国意大利西班牙  想去哪都行
to Europe, France, Italy, Spain, wherever you want to go.
这主意如何
How's that sound?
钥匙在这
Keys are here.
左边  那幢红砖的  一层
Uh, left side, the red brick. First floor.
电池可能没电了  所以可能需要
Battery might be dead, so you might need
-你们所有人推车  -明白了
- all of you to push. - We got it.
维普  你留下跟他一起  我们走
Whip, you stay with him. Let's move.
他总是那样给你发号施令吗
He always give you orders like that?
一言难尽了
It's complicated.
我有个命令给你
I got an order for you.
装车
Load up.
里面还有个包
One more bag inside.
那里
There!
听我的口令一起推
Give it a push on my say.
电池完全没问题
Battery's working perfectly.
停车场有多远
How far away is this garage?
就两个街区远  没问题
Only two blocks. No problem. ‭
只要有人说没问题  就一定会出问题
Someone says there's no problem, there's always a problem.
他给我们下了套  上车
He set us up. ‭Get in!
坐稳
Hold on.
我不是针对你  伙计
Nothing personal, my friend.
要是换种生活环境  我们肯定还在一起抽水烟
In another life, no doubt we smoke the hookah together.
不  别想跑
No! No, you don't!
维普  你还好吗
Whip, you okay?
你还以为你会成百万富翁呢
Thought you were gonna be a millionaire, huh?
我别无选择
I didn't have a choice.
你这人渣敢背后偷袭我
Coldcocking son of a bitch!
等等  等等  冷静  我们可能需要他
Hold on, hold on. Easy now, we may need him.
对  你们需要我
Yes. You need me.
我要去这个费阿刻斯的地图
I want a map to this Phaeacia place.
你知道这里是也门  对吧
You do realize this is Yemen, don't you?
费阿刻斯是个小地方
Phaeacia is a hundred people.
全是小土屋  没有地图
Mud huts. There is no map.
但我可以带你们去
But I can lead you there.
你要相信这个人吗
You want to trust this guy?
如果他耍我们
Well, if he screws with us,
我们就让维普打死他
we'll just let Whip finish what he started.
我绝对会杀了你
And I will kill you.
我等不及要杀他了
I can't wait to kill him.
你敢背后偷袭我  我就灭了你
You coldcock me, I end you.
我们国家的首要原则  懂吗
Rule number one in my country. Okay?
我们国家的首要原则是
And rule number one in my country is
如果大事不妙  那就去沙漠
when things get bad, go to the desert.
我们真是走投无路了
We are desperate, desperate men.
奥马尔比我们更惨
Not as desperate as Omar right now.
他现在惹了最不该惹的人  就是维普
If there's one man you don't want to get on the wrong side of, it's Whip.
这句话也适用于你  迈克尔
That might apply to you, too, Michael.
我感觉那孩子觉得你背叛了他
I get the sense the kid thinks you betrayed him somehow.
我可以理解他为什么这么想
I could understand why he thinks that.
我真的很抱歉  伙计
I really am sorry, my friend.
我一害怕  就会做错选择
When I'm scared, I make poor choices.
懒得听你废话  懂吗
Zero comes out of your mouth. Okay?
我这几天真的过得很不爽  不爽透顶了
I'm having a really bad couple of days. Just the worst.
纽约  国务院附楼
岸田探员
Agent Kishida.
正在收拾新办公室啊
Settling into your new office, I see.
我还觉得这里是凯勒曼的办公室  长官
I still see this as Kellerman's office, ma'am.
或许你已经知道
As you probably know,
在凯勒曼被杀之前
before he was killed,
他一直在调查"21号空间"这个组织
Kellerman had been looking into 21-Void.
是的  我知道
I knew that. Yes.
我需要保罗的文件
I need Paul's files.
显然他快要接近某些真相了
Obviously, he was getting close to something
所以他们杀了他
and they killed him for it.
机密
其实我调查了他的线索
Actually, I've been looking into his leads,
一无所获
and there's nothing there.
我真不想这么说  但这文件里全是死胡同
I hate to say it, but this file is full of dead ends.
机密  仅供过目
这里面什么都没有
There's nothing here.
肯定有点什么
There must be something.
听着  我不希望保罗是白白牺牲
Look, I don't want Paul to have died in vain,
但我们得用全新的视角看这个事件
but we need to look at this whole thing with new eyes.
你自己看吧
Read it for yourself.
好  加入新的看法  行
Okay, you want to put new eyes on this? Fine.
现在我是你上司
Now that you report to me,
我要求你严密观察
I need you to look into the possibility
是否可能有内部人员牵涉其中
that there was an insider involved.
这里  国务院吗
Here? At the State Department?
任何与证据链有关的地方
Anywhere along the evidence chain.
明白  长官
Will do, ma'am.
岸田探员
Agent Kishida.
没想到这个时间打电话过来
I wasn't expecting a call at this hour.
我只是想继续我们早些时候的话题
I just wanted to follow up on our earlier conversation.
中东的情况怎样了
The situation in the Middle East?
情况有了变化
Situation's developing.
我们得尽快见面
We need to meet soon.
好吧
Fair enough.
我们回去了就给你打电话
The moment we're back, we'll call you.
你在国家安全局工作
You worked at NSA?
干了十年的"天眼"监控
Team Eye in the Sky for ten years.
通过卫星看到了你能想到最恶心的勾当
Watched the most heinous crap you can imagine by satellite.
石刑  强奸
Stonings, rapes.
只能坐在那无助地看着
Just had to sit back and watch it
仿佛恐怖电影的东西
like a horror film, helpless,
直到波塞冬接触我
until Poseidon tapped my shoulder,
给了我一个改变现状的机会
gave me a chance to do something about it.
艾米丽  很高兴再次见到你
Emily, good to see you again.
我也是
Likewise.
你收到我的消息了吧
You got my message?
关于卡尼尔·乌提斯的
Kaniel Outis?
你会帮我们找到他们吗
You gonna help us locate them?
听我说  官方回答是不
Look, protocol says no.
我们不参与中情局及一切攻击性质的行动
We stay clear of CIA, any offensive action.
我们只负责监视
We're surveillance only.
我们只想监视他
We just want to put eyes on him.
我想可以以跨部门合作的名义
I think I can get you in as observers
让你们作为观察员加入
under interagency auspices.
我就知道你会帮我
I knew I could count on you.
可你欠我人情
But you owe me.
我们在康涅狄格州住过的那个家庭旅馆
That B&B we went up to in Connecticut,
我要再过一次那样的周末
I want that weekend again.
要一模一样的
That exact weekend.
你这后面装的什么东西
What you got back here, anyway?
这是什么  枪还是毒品
What is this, guns, drugs?
烟火吗
Fireworks?
你不懂费阿刻斯人
You don't understand the Phaeacians.
他们美丽  慷慨
They are beautiful. Generous.
永远在微笑
They just want to smile.
不像你
Unlike you.
是吗
Oh, is that right?
记仇
Ah, holding grudges.
对心脏没有好处
It's very bad for the heart...
你知道还有什么对你的心脏没有好处吗
You know what else is bad for your heart?
我往你心脏里塞一个罗马烟火
If I shove a Roman candle through the middle of it.
雅  拜托
Ja, please.
别当着我们的面嗑药了
Don't check out on us.
还是想不明白你们为什么要救我出来
Still trying to figure out why you got me out.
我需要你的聪明脑袋保持完全清醒
I need that great big mind of yours clean and clear.
是昨晚机场打来的那个号码
It's the number from the airport last night.
钞票哥  怎么样了
C-Note, what's up?
林肯  我是希巴
Lincoln, it's Sheba.
我用的本杰明的电话
I got Benjamin's phone.
你找到奥玛了吗
Did you find Omar?
找到了
Yeah, we found him.
正在赶路
We're traveling.
你还好吗
You okay?
我很好  现在我们在约旦
Yes. We're in Jordan.
今晚飞美国
Leaving for the U.S. tonight.
钞票哥还好吗
How's C-Note?
他很好
He's fine.
我们都好
We all are.
大家都好好的
Everyone.
我们会成功抵达的
We're going to make it.
这都多亏了你
It's because of you.
多亏了我的钱
Because of my money.
是多亏了你
It's because of you.
算了吧
Come on.
你很伟大  林肯
There is nobility in you, Lincoln.
当我回去后  我请你喝一杯
When I get back, I'll, I'll buy you a drink.
我不喝酒的
I don't drink.
但我会请你喝酒
But I'll buy you a drink.
这样如何
How about that?
听起来不错
Sounds good.
约旦  安曼
有结果了
We got a hit;
有人在约旦使用富兰克林的手机
Franklin's cell phone lit up in Jordan.
也门  萨那
几天前他用信用卡在也门买的
The one he bought with a credit card in Yemen a few days ago.
境外呼叫一个未知号码
Making an outbound call to an unknown number.
现在地处也门萨那城外
Currently right outside Sana'a, Yemen.
对该目标重新部署无人机航线
Rerouting a drone to that target now.
我们找到他了  不是吗
We just found our man, didn't we?
那里  两辆车正向西行驶
There. Two vehicles heading west.
无人机已到位
Drones in position.
让我们来看看
Let's take a peek.
他们停下了
They're stopping.
调出该位置的所有资料
Pull up all known data on that location.
为什么停下了
Why did we stop?
离费阿刻斯还有483公里
Phaeacia is 300 miles that way.
我们得加满油
We need to fill our gas tanks up to the top.
迈克尔  你要去哪
Michael, where you going?
过去七年间
Been under Poseidon's thumb
我一直被波塞冬玩弄于鼓掌中
for the last seven years.
是时候摆脱他了
It's about time I got out from under it.
有网吗
Internet?
每分钟100里亚尔[0.4美元]
谢谢
Shukraan.
他们不知道我们在监视他们  对吗
They have no clue we're watching, do they?
在这个高度  不会
Not at this height.
美国中情局打来的电话
你是谁
Who is this?
一位来自远方的朋友
A friend from far away.
你的政府一直把我们视为敌人
Your government has always considered us an enemy.
官方说法而已
Officially.
但我们中有人的想法更开明
But some of us have a more enlightened view.
阿布·拉马尔曾是一位有远见卓识的人
Abu Ramal was a great visionary.
我们向你表示最诚挚的哀悼
You have our sincerest condolences.
你想要什么
What do you want?
和你想要的一样
The same thing you do,
除掉杀了他的凶手
to eliminate the men who killed him.
为表诚意
And as a sign of good faith...
我们会告诉你们他们的确切方位
we'll tell you exactly where they are.
蓝色夏威夷
你能看见我吗
Hey, can you see me?
暂时不能
Not yet.
该死的电脑摄像头
Blasted computer camera thing.
谁造的这鬼玩意儿
Who makes these things?
好了  我看见你了
All right, I see you.
快点  把这个给我解开
Come on, hurry. Get this off of me.
手别动
Hold your hand still.
赶紧动手吧
Just do it already.
你想保持这样吗
Do you want to stay like this?
我们能给你松开是你走了运
You're lucky we cut you loose.
杀了阿布·拉马尔的那些人
The men who killed Abu Ramal,
正在离开萨那  沿80号高速向西行
leaving Sana'a, heading west on Highway 80.
-好的  -80号高速
- Okay. - Highway 80.
我们现在就出发
We're leaving now.
-我也要去  -不
- I'm coming, too. - ‭No.
这不再是你的战斗了
This is not your fight anymore.
明白吗
Understand?
出来  快滚出来
别  求你了
你知道吗  我已经四年没用过空调了
You know it's been four years since I've had air conditioning?
我受够了炎热
I'm done with the heat.
我有点喜欢这里了
Kind of like it out here.
没有高墙
No walls.
没有高墙  这跟墙无关
No walls, okay? Ain't about walls.
在我看来  你知道你在这世上最需要什么吗
My opinion, you know what you need more than anything else in the world?
笑口常开
Got to laugh more.
他要是想笑
If he wants to laugh,
费阿刻斯正是该去的地方
Phaeacia's the place.
我一直想带上希巴
I always wanted to bring Sheba;
让她见见那里的人
for her to see the people.
没有科技  政治  或者现代的荒唐事
No technology, no politics, no modern nonsense.
他们知道该如何享受生活
They know how to enjoy life.
没有科技吗
No technology?
佛莱迪·摩克瑞都黑不进去
Freddie Mercury here couldn't hack it.
佛莱迪·摩克瑞
Freddie Mercury?
我能黑进去
I could hack it.
手机发明前我也活得好好的
I was alive before cell phones.
比起药片  你对手机屏幕
You're more addicted to that screen
更上瘾  这说明了些问题
than you are to them pills, and that is saying something.
准备好
Be ready.
朋友们  我们有麻烦了
My friends. We got problems!
迈克尔  我们得走了
Michael, we got to go!
迈克尔  快走
Michael? Let's go!
我得走了
I got to go.
等一下  让我试试别的办法
Hold on, let me try something else.
你现在能看见我吗
Can you see me now?
不能  截个屏
No. Take a screen capture.
截什么
What of?
截屏  快点
A screen capture. Take it.
ISIL恐怖分子正从东面接近
ISIL militants coming from the east.
这应该会变得很有趣
This should get interesting.
别幻想着一发子弹就能让我们摆脱困境
Don't think one bullet is going to get us out of this.
一发子弹  谁的枪会只带一发子弹
One bullet? Who the hell carries a gun with one bullet?
被ISIL组织抓住前打算饮弹自尽的人
The man who would kill himself before being captured by ISIL.
拉近点  放大
Get closer. Zoom in.
停住
Hold on.
这些士兵是怎么找到他们的
These militants, how'd they find them?
见鬼  你在等什么  回击啊
Damnit, what are you waiting for? Shoot back!
我们只有一发子弹
We only got one bullet.
-一发子弹  -正是
- One bullet? - Exactly.
我们要在这玩完了
We're seriously screwed here.
除非我能让这发子弹发挥效力
Unless I can make this one bullet count.
什么
What?
你果然知道怎么发挥子弹效力  孩子
You sure as hell made it count, kid.
真有你的
Hell yeah, you did.
我的天
Oh, my God.
迈克尔
Michael.
他情况不妙  哥
He's in a bad way, Linc.
来更多人了  我们得赶紧离开这
More coming, we got to get the hell out of here!
他们停下来干什么
What are they stopping for?
不知道
Don't know.
我们不能再往前走了
We can't go any further.
我们还能往前走一大段
We can go a lot further.
我们得赶到费阿刻斯
We've got to get to Phaeacia.
没路了  维普
There's no roads, Whip.
路线和地图在奥玛的脑子里
The roads are in Omar's head along with the map.
我就是这个意思
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
我们的地图已经死了
Our map is dead.
我们得返回
We got to head back.
去哪里
To what?
他说得对
He's right.
没有地图我们会死在这里的
We'll die out there without a map.
那可不一定
We don't know that.
几乎是一定的
We 99% know that.
我猜我们还没脱离险境
Guess we're not out of the woods yet!
我们得甩掉这家伙  无论他是谁
We got to lose this guy, whoever he is!
我们走  快开车  见鬼
Let's go! Then move it, damn it.
现在所有目标方位250
All targets now bearing 2:50.
跟着他们
Stay with them.
不  撤离无人机
No. Pull the drone.
是时候让我们的访客离开了
Time for our visitors to leave.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我们刚在也门发现卡尼尔·乌提斯
We find Kaniel Outis in Yemen,
接着叛军就出现要杀他
and then rebels show up to take him out?
我会觉得那只是巧合吗
Was I supposed to think that was a coincidence?
这不是监视  对吗
This isn't surveillance, is it?
这是暗杀
This is assassination.
你在利用我干一些见不得光的勾当  对吗
You're using me for some sort of black work, aren't you?
这是你无需过问的  特里西亚
This is way over your head, Tricia.
别再问问题
Stop asking questions.
如果你还不走  我就要告发你了
If you don't get out of my sight, I will blow the whistle.
马上
Right now.
原本我俩在康涅狄格州的周末会很销魂
Would've been a hell of a weekend in Connecticut.
美国国家安全局
这是玩火
It's playing with fire,
像这样私自占用其他部门资源
co-opting other agencies like that.
你觉得她会告发吗
You think she'll talk?
大打国家牌来试探我们吗
Run it up the flagpole?
你想杀了她吗
You got designs on killing her?
我会杀了你
I'll kill you.
别紧张  好吧
Relax, will you?
我已经厌倦追踪乌提斯了
I'm getting pretty tired of chasing Outis.
-总是跟在他屁股后面  -我也是
- Always being behind him. - Me, too.
所以我一直在想
That's why I keep thinking about all that time
他在也门加油站时的事
that he spent in that gas station in Yemen.
ISIL的人对他紧追不舍
ISIL on his tail,
而他却还在那里待着
and he just hangs in there?
他在那里做什么
What was he doing in there?
太阳在我们正上方
The sun is directly overhead.
我分不出哪边是东  哪边是西
I can't tell which way is east, west...
我们得停车
We got to stop.
雅  你手机上有没有指南针
Hey, Ja. You got a compass on that phone?
没信号
No signal.
我们这是在瞎开
We're flying blind.
完全瞎开
Completely blind.
但他不是
But he's not.
我们留下了漂亮的轮胎印让他跟
We're leaving him a beautiful set of tire tracks to follow.
这家伙到底是什么人
Who the hell is this guy?
就是他杀了希德
It's the guy who killed Sid.
这混蛋就是只死咬不放的狗
Son of a bitch is like a dog with a bone, huh?
你杀了人家的精神领袖
You kill someone's spiritual leader,
他们显然会追杀你到天涯海角
they'll follow you to the ends of the Earth, apparently.
他为什么停下了
Why is he stopping?
他在加油
He's refueling.
现在加什么油
Now?
他知道自己的汽油比我们多
He knows he's got more gas than we do.
他只用跟着我们的轮胎印走
All he has to do is follow our tracks.
然后等着我们把油用完
Then wait until we run out.
我们有四个人
There are four of us.
我们可以围住他然后干掉他
Let's just swarm him, take him out.
在这里可不行
Not out here.
人家手里可端着AK-47呢
Not with an AK-47.
我们没法在不挨子弹的情况下
We wouldn't get within a hundred feet of him
跑进他三十米内的地方
without taking a bullet.
那么我们只能智取他
Then we got to outthink him.
你要怎么做  抽他吗
What you gonna do with that, flog him?
把那辆车油箱的油加到这个油箱里
Gonna transfer gas from that tank to this one.
差不多全部的油
Almost all of it.
这没用
It's not gonna help.
可以让这辆车开到费阿刻斯
It's gonna help this one get to Phaeacia.
我们挤在一辆车里吗
We pile into one vehicle?
他的汽油还是比我们多
He still has more gas than us.
他还是可以跟着我们的轮胎印走
He can still follow our tire tracks.
所以我们才要给这辆车留一点汽油
That's why we leave a little bit of gas in that one.
留下两套轮胎印
And make two sets of tracks.
他就要做出选择
He's gonna have to choose.
我手里有四颗石头
I got four rocks in my hand.
三颗红的  一颗白的
Three red, one white.
拿到红石头的坐上吉普车  去费阿刻斯
Get the red rock, get in the Jeep, go to Phaeacia.
拿到白石头的
Get the white rock,
去搞定我们的"朋友"
deal with our friend.
把手伸出来
Stick out your hand.
红色
Red.
维普
Whip.
快点
Come on.
红色
Red.
哥
Linc.
不
No.
你知道规矩的  哥
You knew the rules, Linc.
他又要追上来了
He's picking up again.
我不能把你留在这里等死
I'm not leaving you out here to die.
我也没打算死
I have no intention of dying.
总之  你的任务更艰巨
Anyway, you've got the harder job.
你得去找到费阿刻斯的所在地
You've got to find Phaeacia out there somewhere.
留下记号  好让我找到你
Leave tracks so I know how to find you.
就一辆
Just one.
想玩是吗  你个贱人
You want to play, you son of a bitch?
我该怎么甩掉这个"尾巴"
Now how the hell am I gonna get out of this?
我们根本是无头苍蝇瞎开
We're driving blind.
这周围怎么看都一个样
It's the same damn thing everywhere we look.
这自有它的好处
There's something to be said for that.
充分调动你的感官
Makes you use your senses.
你能别再胡扯了吗
Will you stop talking crap
还是说说大家避之不及的话题
and talk elephant in the room, please?
我们刚丢下了迈克尔
We just left Michael back there.
这样做大错特错了
It's completely wrong.
你最不该跟我说这话
I'm the last guy you want to say that to.
那我们为什么这么做
Well, why are we doing it, then?
因为这是他的决定
Because he said, that's why.
有一件事你不理解
One thing you don't understand.
当迈克尔对抗全世界时
When Michael takes on the world,
输的总是全世界
the world always loses.
我们一直在找
We've been looking the whole time.
这才是问题
That's the problem.
什么
What?
关闭引擎
Stop the engine.
听到了吗
You hear that?
鸟鸣吗
Birds?
不是一般的鸟  是海鸥
Not just birds. Gulls.
据我所知  海鸥对沙漠没兴趣
As far as I know, gulls got no interest in the desert.
它们只喜欢海洋
They only got interest in the sea.
这说明我们离海很近了  只要跟着它们就行
It means we're close. All you got to do is follow them.
或许最终我们还是有"指向标"的
Maybe we got GPS after all.
这里是费阿刻斯吗
Is this Phaeacia?
费阿刻斯  费阿刻斯
Phaeacia! Phaeacia!
费阿刻斯
Phaeacia!
奥玛  奥玛
Omar! Omar!
Omar, Omar.
你好
Hello.
你开的是奥玛的车  但你不是奥玛
You bring Omar car, but not Omar?
奥玛去了安全的地方
Omar had to go somewhere safe.
因为战争吗
Because of the war?
是的  战争  没错
Yeah, the war. That's right.
他让我们把这些东西带给你
He told us to bring this stuff for you.
他还说让你替我们找船
Also said you could arrange a boat for us.
在城里那会儿
Back in the city...
我就告诉过你你会死
I told you you would die.
我们都要死在这里了  美国人
We will both die out here, American!
看来萨那外面的加油站
Turns out that gas station outside Sana'a
缅因州  波特兰市
有台联网的电脑
had a computer with Internet access.
他从也门发来了这张照片  为什么
He sent this image from Yemen. Why?
我们跟他发送图片的人谈过就知道了
We're gonna find out as soon as we talk to the guy he sent it to.
在缅因州波特兰的蓝色夏威夷
Blue Hawaii in Portland, Maine.
你觉得他是来这过冬吗
Think we got a snowbird?
可能并不只是如此
I don't think that's quite it.
欢迎来到格雷斯兰
Welcome to Graceland.
别站在那里把冷气都放走了
Don't just stand there and let the AC out.
快进来
Come on in.
我能为你们做些什么
What can I do for you fine folks?
哥  你的轮胎印在哪里
Linc, where are your tracks?
轮胎印  轮胎印
Tracks, tracks.
不  不  不
No, no, no, no!
No, no. No.
动起来啊  快
Come on. Come on!
振作起来  迈克  要振作
Come on, Mike, come on.
轮胎印在哪里
Where are the tracks?
这是给你的  看
This is for you. Look.
等等  慢点  慢点
W-Wait, go easy, go easy.
从小东西开始
Start with the small stuff.
花  蛇  晚点给你们看火炮
Flowers, snakes, we'll move onto the artillery later.
-烟花可以吗  好用吗  -当然
- Fireworks okay? It's okay to use?  - Yes, yes, of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
奥玛是对的
Omar was right.
这地方
This place.
就好像世外桃源
It's like the rest of the world doesn't exist.
我去看看林肯
I'll go check on Linc.
还好吗
Hanging in there?
你说得对  我本不该丢下他
You're right. I shouldn't have abandoned him.
如果他入夜之前找不到那些轮胎印
If he doesn't find those tire tracks by nightfall,
他就再也找不到了
he never will.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
去找他
Going out to find him.
晚上不能去
You can't go out there at night.
你永远找不到他
You'll never find him.
我不可能什么都不做
Doing nothing's not an option.
我没让你什么都不做
I didn't say do nothing.
你要有信念
You got to have faith.
莎拉
Sarah.
迈克尔
Michael!
结束了
That's it.
迈克尔
Michael.
谢天谢地  你撑过来了
Thank God, you made it.
他给我下了毒
He poisoned me.
-什么  -防冻液
- What?! - Antifreeze.
需要医生
Need a doctor.
现在就去找个医生
Get the doctor now.
唯一的医生在萨那
The doctor, the only doctor is in Sana'a.
我们不可能回到萨那
We can't go back to Sana'a.
我们刚从那里过来
We just came from there.
要穿越483公里的沙漠
It's 300 miles across the friggin' desert.
我们得想想办法  他要死了
We got to do something. He's dying.
迈克尔  迈克尔
Michael, Michael.
越 狱 第五季第六集